## **EMMANUEL UGOCHUKWU**



Web Developer & Graphic Designer

I am a creative, hard working Full-Stack developer and graphic designer who stands out from others. I've got a unique mix of creativity, time management, problem solving, and technical skill, proven by 4+ years of experience. Excellent communicator, quick to grasp the bigger picture.



Github.com/Dezigndoctor



### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Freelance Web Developer

#### 2021-Present

Upwork Inc

- · Built an ecommerce webapp to sell potty training advent calendars.
- Designed a customer web form for a medical labouratory office.
- Developeped a job listing website for a startup firm.
- Created a website for local food delivery resturant

#### **Graphic Designer**

#### 2018-2020

Hiconnect Prints, Nsukka.

- Responsible for daily designing of customers content requests.
- Created wireframes and page designs for multiple client websites.
- Used Illustrator, and Photoshop daily to produce designs, Frequently integrated photographic, typographic, and graphic elements

#### **Graphic Designer**

#### 2015-2017

Apollos Studios, University of Nigeria, Nsukka

- Responsible for daily design graphiccontents in the firm.
- Responsible for editing studio pictures for clients.
- · Creating LOGOs, 3D designs, social media flyers, and bussines branding for clients.



### **COURSES COMPLETED**

**Web Development Bootcamp** 

**Ultimate Adobe Photoshop Training** 

The Complete Full-Stack JavaScript Course

**After Effects: Complete Course from Novice to Expert** 

Adobe Illustrator CC - Essentials Training Course



# SKILLS

HTML

**CSS** 

**JavaScript** 

SOL

React.is

Node.js

**PHOTOSHOP** 

**ILLUSTRATOR** 

AFTER EFFECTS



# **EDUCATION**

**B Eng. Electronic Engineering** University of Nigeria, Nsukka



## **INTERESTS**

Codina Chess Video games Football